KRIDCHASORN PRAMSRILO

Front-end Developer

➅ Chonburi, Thailand 20000

+66 (0) 88 529 9400

kridchasorn.psl98@gmail.com

https://github.com/Lottaltz

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ kridchasorn-pramsrilo-work

Technical Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Bootstrap

Tailwind

React

Node.js

Express.js

MongoDB

SQL

Figma

Photoshop

Behavioural Skills

Active Listening

Adabtability

Collaborative

Communication

Customer Service

Decision Making

Empathy

Negotiation

Orientation to detail

Persistance

Proactiveness

Problem Solving

Responsibility

Self-Learning

Stress Management

Teamwork

Time Management

Education

Diploma in Businees Computer (march2023)

Aksorn Pattaya Technological College,

Chonburi, Thailand

Personal Summary

I am a graduate of Generation's Junior Software Developer Bootcamp looking for a full stack developer position. I have 5+ years of work experience in retail customer services. Which allowed me to develop communication, negotiation, teamwork and coordination skills. I am eager to apply my previous work experiences and newly developed technical skills to launch my career in the tech sector.

Experience

Junior Software Developer Bootcamp Cohort 5 (July 2023 - Oct 2023)

Generation Thailand

- Learned how to build web applications from React as front-end, Node.js as back-end, and MongoDB as a Database.
- Learned essential skills for switching careers, such as growth mindset, communication, agile, and teamwork.
- Created a project use MERN stack with team.

This project is an application website which service user for their sport activity. In front-end, We used React with React-router and Axios as the main dependency. In the back-end, it uses Express to manage RESTful API. Finally, using Mongoose to connect MongoDB database.

Store Manager (Jan 2019 - Dec 2021)

7-ELEVEN Convenience Store

- Collaborated with warehouses and suppliers to track and control product quality.
- Conducted quality checks on all products before delivering them to customers.
- Prepared monthly plans and established team goals.
- Adapted the work plan based on the current situation.
- Managed internal and external pressures.
- Efficiently managed time to ensure successful plan execution.

Assistant Store Manager (Nov 2017 - Jan 2019)

7-ELEVEN Convenience Store

- Managed team tasks towards common goals and ensured goal adherence.
- Supervised team members, maximizing their preparedness for work.
- Maintained order, safety, and equipment availability in the store.
- Addressed and resolved initial customer problems and complaints prior to escalation.

Sales Clerk (Nov 2016 - Nov 2017)

7-ELEVEN Convenience Store

- Delivered exceptional customer service while handling a high volume of customers.
- Handled payments for goods or bills and provided advice on various promotions.
- Organized store products using the first in, first out principle.
- Kept updated on new products or services to enhance customer assistance.